audio4fun.com 2018-09-08

# Audio4fun.com privacy policy

Last updated: 18 Feb 2016

#### Everyone's and anyone's privacy must be respected!

At the _**[ Audio4fun.com store](https://www.audio4fun.com/policy/legal.htm "All websites/ channels/ stores that sell software products from AVnex")**_, we are committed to protecting your privacy. When you visit our website, we may automatically collect your Internet Protocol address (IP address) or cookies to enable us to provide better services that will be more suitable to you. Unless you provide, we do not collect your name or e-mail address. We do not follow your browsing path outside **Audio4fun.com**.

However, when you purchase a product, we ask you to provide personal information for our bank to process your order.

#### For what purpose and when does Audio4fun.com collect personal information?

When you contact us, we need only an email address which we use to send the information you requested.

We may also use the information we collect to occasionally notify you about new Audio4fun.com's products and special offers we think you'll find valuable. Should you do not want to receive this information, confirm it through an email to us.

When you place an order, you will be transferred to our online retailer - **Avangate** \- to process your order. At this page, you will have to provide your name, email address, mailing address, and credit informatioon - however, rest assure that these information are stored and processed at highest secure level.

As a software product vendor, we will collect your name, email address, mailing address, and the serial number (the license). We use these information for further support your product accordingly.

#### How we use online advertisements:

We advertise Audio4fun on the Google content network using Google's remarketing technology across the internet. In doing this, we hope to attract visitors back to our site that have previously visited Audio4fun and who have previously begun, but not finished, one or more tasks. 

Google AdWords Remarketing will display ads based on the content you have viewed on www.audio4fun.com by leaving a cookie in your machine. This cookie does not in any way identify you or give anyone access to your computer. Google AdWords Remarketing allows us to tailor our marketing to better suit your needs and will only display ads that are relevant to you.

This could be in the form of an advertisement on a Google search result page, or on a site that uses the Google display network. Third-party vendors, including Google, may use cookies to display ads based on a person's past visits to Audio4fun's website. 

#### How to opt out of Google's use of cookies:

If you do not wish to participate in our Google AdWords Remarketing, you can opt out of Google's use of cookies by visiting Google's [Ads Settings](https://www.google.com/settings/ads "Ads Settings"), or by visiting the [Network Advertising Initiative op-out page](https://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/ "Network Advertising Initiative op-out page") to opt out of a third-party vendor's use of cookies.

#### Will Audio4fun.com disclose the information it collects to outside parties?

We do not sell, trade, rent or lease your personal information to others.

#### Your consent

By using the _**Audio4fun.com store**_ , you consent to the collection and use of this information by AVSoft Corp. as described in this Policy. If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it. 

#### Other terms and conditions

In the event that you desire to purchase our products, the software, you must agree not to use the software in any manner that is illegal, unethical, harassing, threatening, intimidating, abusive, obscene, profane, defamatory, hateful or a nuisance.

Software piracy is theft. Using and distributing **AV Voice Changer Software** crack, **AV Music Morpher** crack, **AV WebCam Morpher** crack, **AV Video Morpher** crack, illicit password, serial numbers, protection numbers, activation keys, hack, key generators (keygens), warez prevent future software development.

Under no circumstances shall AVSoft Corp. be liable for any indirect, incidental or consequential damages or any liability in tort, contract, or other legal theory for computer failure or malfunction, business interruption, loss of profits, loss of goodwill, or any other damages or losses arising out of your use or inability to use the software.

Should you have any question concerning this Policy, please [contact us via this form](https://www.audio4fun.com/contact.htm).
